import {Question} from "./question.model";

export const questions: Question[] = [
  {
    question: `What is your secret drug while studying`,
    solution: 'chewinggum',
    correctCharPosition: 6,
  },
  {
    question: `What is Sophie doing at 10pm at a party`,
    solution: 'sleeping',
    correctCharPosition: 6,
  },
  {
    question: `Wie fühlt sich die Anja, wenn etwas schräges passiert?`,
    solution: 'uuuuunangenehm',
    correctCharPosition: 6,
  },
  {
    question: `Wofür ist Maxi bekannt?`,
    solution: 'pupsen',
    correctCharPosition: 5,
  },
  {
    question: `Dein Spitzname`,
    solution: 'ilos',
    correctCharPosition: 3,
  },
  {
    question: `What is Georg doing the day before moving to be perfectly prepared`,
    solution: 'drinking',
    correctCharPosition: 4,
  },
  {
    question: `Bergis Markenzeichen`,
    solution: 'stinkefinger',
    correctCharPosition: 6,
  },
  {
    question: `What did Kshitij lose in Amsterdam?`,
    solution: 'pants',
    correctCharPosition: 4,
  },
  {
    question: `What do Max & Flo have in common?`,
    solution: 'sweating',
    correctCharPosition: 2,
  },
  {
    question: `how Chirag sends his dick-pics?`,
    solution: 'decoration',
    correctCharPosition: 4,
  },
  {
    question: `What is Kshitij doing when he's kuddeling spoon position with Eloise?`,
    solution: 'farting',
    correctCharPosition: 1,
  },
  {
    question: `Whate are you famous for? Another nickname...`,
    solution: 'enzyklopedia',
    correctCharPosition: 7,
  },
  {
    question: `Maxi's Lieblingsbuch`,
    solution: 'gutscheinbuch',
    correctCharPosition: 11,
  },
  {
    question: 'Ferdinand von und zu Schnurbeins richtiger Name',
    solution: 'carl',
    correctCharPosition: 3
  }
]

export const result: Question = {
  question: '',
  solution: '9124',
  correctCharPosition: 5
}
